http://www.addictionrecoveryguide.org/privacy

RECOMMENDED READING
Climbing Mountains: Inspiring stories about substance misuse recovery in NottinghamEdited by Paula Torres-Silva, Celandor Books 2011
Eight Step Recovery: Using the Buddha's Teachings to Overcome AddictionValerie Mason-John
The Sky is Green and the Grass is Blue: Turning Your Upside Down World Right Side UpDeb Scott
Privacy Statement
THE ADDICTION RECOVERY GUIDE
Website Privacy Statement
Effective: 3/12/12
(the "Privacy Statement")
1. ACKNOWLEDGEMENT AND ACCEPTANCE OF TERMS
THE ADDICTION RECOVERY GUIDE is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement, effective March 12, 2012 sets forth our current privacy practices with regard to the information we collect when you or your computer interact with our website. By accessing the THE ADDICTION RECOVERY GUIDE website at www.addictionrecoveryguide.com and www.addictionrecoveryguide.org (the "Website"), you acknowledge and agree to the terms of this Website Privacy Statement and freely consent to the information collection and use practices described in this Website Privacy Statement.
2. INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT
THE ADDICTION RECOVERY GUIDE website collects certain information from and about its users two ways: directly from our Web Server logs and the user.
a. Web Server Logs
When you visit our Website, we may track certain information to administer the Website and analyze its usage. Examples of information we may track include:
Your Internet protocol address.
The kind of browser or computer you use.
Number of links you click within the Website.
State or country from which you accessed the Website.
Date and time of your visit.
Name of your Internet service provider.
Web page you linked to our Website from.
Pages you viewed on the Website.
b. Personal Information
Personal Information can be submitted in two ways: by completing and submitting a contact form and by using the Message Board.
1. Contact Forms
All information submitted on our contact forms is immediately sent to us by email but is not stored on this website.
2. Message Board
Information submitted on our message board is stored on this website indefinitely. Some of this information, like passwords, are private and only accessible by our database administrator, who may occasionally access it only when identifying and addressing technical problems. Other information, like username and public posts are accessible to the general public. If your computer allows, we may place a small text file, called a "cookie", in your web browser’s files, for allowing you to login into your optionally created message board account. Please be aware that information you post on any online discussion is public and may be seen or collected by third parties that do not adhere to our privacy policy, and therefore this privacy statement does not protect you when you use any of addictionrecoveryguide.com/.org’s message board forums. You should have no expectation of privacy when you participate in an online discussion group on this or any website.
We will not disclose any personally identifiable information from you to third parties without your permission except to the extent necessary including:
To fulfill your service requests for services.
To protect ourselves from liability.
To respond to legal process or comply with law.
3. CHANGES TO THIS STATEMENT
THE ADDICTION RECOVERY GUIDE has the sole discretion to occasionally update this Privacy Statement. When updated, the "updated" date at the top of this Privacy Statement will be revised. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service on the Website constitutes your continuing agreement to this Privacy Statement and any updates.
4. CONTACTING US
If you have questions regarding our Privacy Statement, its implementation, and/or our general practices, please contact us or send comments to: info@addictionrecoveryguide.com.
Attention: Privacy Statement Personnel
THE ADDICTION RECOVERY GUIDE will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly respond and resolve any problem or question.
